A Finding Aid to the Ivan C. Karp Personal Papers and OK Harris Works of Art gallery records, 1960-2014, in the Archives of American Art AAA.okharr
Archives of American Art
- Ivan C. Karp Personal Papers, 1961-2012; Series 8; 4 Linear feet Boxes 75-79
  - Journals (Box 77)
    - Travel Journals (Box 77)
      - Brussels, France, Italy, Yugoslavia, Turkey, Greece, Bulgaria, Roumania, Czechoslovakia, Russia, Poland (1964 June-August), 2007 (Box 77, Folder 8)
      - Omaha, Reno (1968 June), 2007 (Box 77, Folder 9)
      - Guatemala, Panama (1976 February), 2007 (Box 77, Folder 10)
      - France (1977); Prague, Budapest (1978); Spain (1980); Italy (1981); Tunisia (198)]; France (1982), (1977 May-1982 June), 2007 (Box 77, Folder 11)
      - Southern Spain, England, Paris, Las Vegas (1983 February-September), 2007 (Box 77, Folder 12)
      - Sicily (1983 December), 2007 (Box 77, Folder 13)
      - Egypt;Haiti, Palm Beach, Las Vegas, Paris; Italy; Nice, Monaco; Knoxville, Guatemala (1984 December-1984 March)[1987], 2007 (Box 77, Folder 14)
      - Las Vegas; England, Las Vegas, Salt Lake City, Moscow, Leningrad; Las Vegas, Paris, Israel; Nashville, Southwest, Las Vegas, Santa Barbara, Albuquerque (1987 September-1990 December), 2007 (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Daily Journals (Box 77)
      - Volume 1 (1991 February 4-1991 November 7), 2007 (Box 77, Folder 16)
      - Volume 2 (1991 November 8-1992 August 10), 2007 (Box 77, Folder 17)
      - Volume 3 (1992 August 11-1993 April 1), 2007 (Box 77, Folder 18)
      - Volume 4 (1993 April 1-1994 August 18), 2007 (Box 77, Folder 19-20)
      - Volume 5 (1994 August 19-1995 March 22), 2007 (Box 77, Folder 21-22)
      - Volume 6 (1995 March 23-1995 September 11), 2007 (Box 77, Folder 23-24)
      - Volume 7 (1995 September 12-1996 February 28), 2007 (Box 77, Folder 25)
      - Volume 8 (1996 February 29-1996 July 9), 2007 (Box 77, Folder 26)
      - Volume 9 (1996 July 10-1996 November 3), 2007 (Box 77, Folder 27)
      - Volume 10 (1996 November 4-1997 April 20, 2007 (Box 77, Folder 28)
      - Volume 11 (1997 April 22-1997 August 18), 2007 (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - Volume 12 (1997 August 19-1998 January 21), 2007 (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - Volume 13 (1998 January 22-1998 June 24), 2007 (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - Volume 14 (1998 June 25-1998 October 12), 2007 (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - Volume 15 (1998 October13-1999 April 9), 2007 (Box 78, Folder 5)
      - Volume 16 (1999 April 10-1999 August 9), 2007 (Box 78, Folder 6)
      - Volume 17 (1999 August 10- 1999 December 29), 2007 (Box 78, Folder 7)
      - Volume 18 (1999 December 30-2000 June 13), 2007 (Box 78, Folder 8)
      - Volume 19 (2000 June 14-2000 September 11), 2007 (Box 78, Folder 9)
      - Volume 20 (2000 September 12-2001 May 4), 2007 (Box 78, Folder 10)
      - Volume 21 (2001 May 5-2001 September 28), 2007 (Box 78, Folder 11)
      - Volume 22 (2001 September 29-2002 June 9), 2007 (Box 78, Folder 12)
      - Volume 23 (2002 June 10-2002 September 28), 2007 (Box 78, Folder 13)
      - Volume 24 (2002 October 7-2003 April 30), 2007 (Box 78, Folder 14)
      - Volume 25 (2003 May 1-2003 August 8), 2007 (Box 78, Folder 15)
      - Volume 26 (2003 August 8-2004 February 3), 2007 (Box 78, Folder 16)
      - Volume 27 (2004 February 4-2004 June 26), 2007 (Box 78, Folder 17)
      - Volume 28 (2004 June 27-2004 November 10), 2007 (Box 78, Folder 18)
      - Volume 29 (2004 November 11-2005 May 22), 2007 (Box 78, Folder 19)
      - Volume 30 (2005 May 23-2005 August 22), 2012 (Box 78, Folder 20)
      - Volume 31 (2005 August 23-2006 January 27), 2012 (Box 78, Folder 21)
      - Volume 32 (2006 January 29-2006 June 23), 2012 (Box 78, Folder 22)
      - Volume 33 (2006 June 24-2007 January 20), 2012 (Box 79, Folder 1)
      - Volume 34 (2007 January 21-2007 June 29), 2012 (Box 79, Folder 2)
      - Volume 35 (2007 June 30-2008 March 11), 2012 (Box 79, Folder 3)
      - Volume 36 (2008 March 13-2008 July 11), 2012 (Box 79, Folder 4)
      - Volume 37 (2008 July 12-2009 January 21), 2012 (Box 79, Folder 5)
      - Volume 38 (2009 January 22-2009 December 30), 2012 (Box 79, Folder 6)
      - Volume 39 (2010 January -2012 June 13) (Box 79, Folder 7)
      - Loose Pages (circa 1993-circa 1997), circa 2007 (Box 79, Folder 8)